Look, guys, it's Caputo!
Where's Rika?
Rika is... not here?
Then that means the movie isn't here either.
Yep.
This is so stupid.
She messaged me late last night saying it would be done today no matter what
and we had nothing to worry about.
So dramatic.
Hold on.
Does that mean she pulled an all-nighter again?
I'm gonna go check on her.
Rika, you in there?
What the?
Why is it unlocked?
Rika?
Uh, Rika!
Rika!
the doctor said it was just a cold okay seriously she didn't have to worry us like that
i was thinking is it possible we put too much pressure on her by letting her edit the whole
thing by herself maybe whatever we don't have time to waste worrying about that now
how is that a waste of time we can't do anything about it we have work to do
what are we going to work on we have to cancel all the screenings cancel them such a waste of good
close-ups it's not finished what else are we supposed to do besides it's pointless to have
a premiere of the movie when all seven of us aren't there i agree
no touching mitts off the bulletin board it's sacred oh kotika i didn't recognize you
hey it's okay aoi didn't mean to freak you out like that something came up and my group had
to cancel the presentation so i was taking down the posters my bad hey guess what remember that
time i accused you of touching the bulletin board and you didn't that was dumb you're not the kind
of guy who would do that i'm sorry but this is so lame i'm not trying to pansy out but you might be
the first person ever to believe that i'm not trying to ruin their lives i'm not trying to
understand anything you're saying right now but it's obvious your heart is as sweet as the nose
on your perfect little face no wonder you and sen are together you're like an angel mouse couple
straight out of a pastry cart i could eat you alive put that in park sen is not my girlfriend we're in
a club together not possible i know sen akasha wasaki and homegirl's not in any club she is but
it's only been since june huh the neighbors club i've never heard of this and i've got at least four
neighbors what are you guys doing there uh we uh right now we just take these posters down
right i'm sorry i didn't mean to keep you all good okay i guess i'll see you later
rika are you awake yes there's plenty of room for you in here of course there is you know that joke's
getting old
wow maybe you shouldn't get better why do you want rika to keep suffering from a terminal illness
no i was just joking you guys aren't showing the movie at all anymore no but rika was so close to
finishing it there's no point in making you do that if you just end up back in here fine but it's
seriously almost done you guys could show what we have and nobody would ever know don't be silly
we're not gonna do that
we can't have a premiere of a movie we all worked on if not all of us are there
that's what yozura said yozura said that yeah i was shocked too at first but i agree with her
we all do so there
sorry did that throw off your game face don't be silly everything's fine
are you sure when she told me i almost cried
rika has a comment now's a good time for you to take advantage of rika
she's half asleep it's fine you're insane do you have a backup plan in case i ever take you up on
one of your smutty offers no rika knows you won't
oh rika just had the best idea ever you should read one of her books to her until she falls asleep
oh yeah yeah how about this one
you want me to read you boy love not happening please it's really good and rika's dying
you're so ridiculous it'll make rika feel better you're her only hope
oh fine you pervert but i'm gonna talk to your doctor about this other sickness you have
the things i do for you
this is really going to help rika oh good you found the bookmark you can start from the top of the page
right uh okay so he said i know that you want it bad
poor you've been so desperate for my boy hole my ass is hungry teacher and wants a bite of your
uh a bite of your speak up this is the best part uh wants a bite of your sweet delicious cocksicle
commit rika needs to believe you he was aroused he often caressed himself to thoughts of that yaoi hole
and now here he would destroy it the heck is a yaoi hole like a secret compartment on his body
if you're a boy and you don't know what the yaoi hole is is this real life
huh huh
i asked you first
ana
rika can't believe the yaoi hole doesn't really exist
and what made you think of this
how is rika supposed to know differently
she's never actually seen a boy naked in real life
and she doesn't have any friends who want to talk to her about it much less show her
do you have one and aren't telling rika just show her one time
you need to get some sleep i gotta go anyway
okay
it's cool that we can joke around like this and things don't get weird
i'm really glad we're friends rika
you get made rika has great news for you guys
the movie is finally finished so let's meet in the club room
whoa
rika knows that she inconvenienced all of you at the school festival the other day
and she wants to apologize
you mean ruining it
no problem we're all glad you're feeling better
i just want to see my face so can we get on with this
yeah come on i can't wait to see our big movie
show us your fruitless efforts
if you dare tragic mortal
okay i hope you guys enjoy
okay
oh
whoa
I
Guess that's it. It's kind of like our own private neighbors club school festival
Oh
Voices you're too loud
Yeah, don't beat my high score
Who is that I use that we're in the same class you self-centered hag
Huh are you sure yeah, you even asked me what time it was in homeroom once
How that you're this close your squeaky tone does sound familiar
How does the universe even allow you to keep living so is there something we can help you with or did you just want to talk to Senate?
I almost forgot
You wait right here
I need to know what goes on in this club. All I ever see you do is play
This is called taking a break put your claws back in don't waste your time trying to cover it up
I've been keeping tabs on you jerks for months now. So there really what for I wanted to see what club both
You and Sina would be in since it seemed freakish that you'd be into the same things. Oh, is it really that suspicious?
And what if we did just play games? What business is it of yours each club has its own agenda?
The only ones who should have that info are club members
Outsiders have no right to question us. I'm on the student council lady pants. It's my job to enforce rules here and your violation
This is awkward. I'm pretty sure she's only here to mess with Sina their rivals or something
That figures
Look pinky the neighbors club is officially recognized by the school our club rules and practices have been reviewed and approved in compliance with God's law
We vow to embrace everyone as neighbors deepen friendships on a spiritual level and treat everyone with the kindness that God wants
Love thy neighbor as thyself in layman's terms that means
Hanging out and playing games together strengthens our bond. We are following the club rules
What how the hell did she remember that sure we play video games we read but it's all about spending quality time with each other and making friends
Isn't that what everyone wants?
Isn't that what you want to someone that you can depend on someone cool?
You can always hang out with someone smart. You can learn from
Someone like me. It's not about you. We work very hard to make sure we're being as friendly and neighborly as possible to our members and other students
Well, I do think having friends help students get through school and makes life more fun and easier to deal with
But I think you guys are doing a crappy job and should be shut down. That sounds like a personal issue to me
I mean is the student council even allowed to make club rulings based on someone's hurt ego
It's not that look at her she is in violation of school policy and so is that one school rules override
Club rules what are you talking about the dress code?
It's all here in the handbook article five specifically list the rules for attire here
It is students are required to wear their uniform at all times while on campus as well as to and from school uniform includes pleated skirt
Yeah, keep reading you'll see that section four of article five was several exceptions
One of them is that approved club meetings don't count so we can wear street clothes
Two, three, four
Oh crap
You idiot that rule only applies to gym clothes which are technically still part of the uniform
Then someone needs to get the handbook amended because I know it doesn't say gym clothes specifically
Your book of human laws has no power over me mortal
Yeah, you're lucky you're still in middle school
Who's in middle school?
Violation she is not allowed to be in here
I am too
Check your book there's no rule that says you have to be a certain age to join a club
You know very well that outsiders aren't allowed on campus much less in the building
Yeah, it does say outsiders aren't allowed on property even if accompanied by a legal student
Okay then
However, middle schoolers are not considered outsiders
They may go to school on a different campus but they're still students of St. Chronica's Academy, right?
But more importantly, since when is your own brother or sister considered an outsider?
And let's talk about this chapel
Yeah, it's on campus, it's open to the public
Anyone can come in here at any time whether they're 13 or 90
Which means someone who's a student and sister of a member in a public location can't be an outsider
What she said
You're okay
This isn't over, I'm gonna think of something
Come here, shoes
Is there anything we can do to make sure she doesn't come back?
Conversations with stupid people make me want to throw up
Presidential wisdom
Good work
Get ready to pack up because I got you this time
Gross, do you still exist?
I really am over your pointless cockiness
I happen to find a section that says this neighbor's club crap is definitely in violation of school rules
Huh
My god, you're obsessed
Section 2, rules for extracurricular activities
Look, right here it says
As a rule, classes, clubs, and other activities undertaken in groups must be conducted under the supervision of an instructor
That just means we have to have an advisor present at all the meetings, doesn't it?
Yeah, and you don't have an advisor present
Huh?
It says here in article 78
Student council bylaws say that club advisors must be faculty or staff of the school
Right, because in section 2 it says that a sister's authority is equal to that of any faculty member on campus
So yeah, we're all good there
Um, how?
You don't have a sister you can call an advisor
I hope you weren't referring to Maria Takayama during that speech
Cause she's not an actual sister
Huh?
That's right, I checked the roster of sisters thoroughly
There is absolutely no Maria Takayama listed
There is someone registered with that last name and it's her sister Kate
Which means Maria here is just a random little girl who hangs out in a chapel illegally
Huh?
No freaking way
We listed her as our club advisor and it was approved
Someone on staff made a mistake
Hold on, I'm gonna clear this up
Hey, Broseph, what's up?
I need your help with something
Maria's a sister, right?
Like she's legit?
No
Huh? What do you mean?
She's my assistant, but it's not official
I'm just trying to help her develop the skills for when she gets older
Plus it's easier for me to keep an eye on her if she's at the same school
But why does she tell everyone she's a teacher?
I don't know, great imagination, I guess
She wears the nun outfit every freaking day
Cause it's adorable
Apparently it's true, she's not a real sister
Well, that sucks
Man, talk about a bubble being busted
But if I'm not a real sister, then what am I?
That's right, turd faces
You don't have an advisor
And if you don't have an advisor, you don't have a legitimate club
If you're trying to form a club illegally, then you're trying to get disbanded
And if that's not what you're looking for
If Maria were an official advisor, we'd be all good, right?
Yeah, but she isn't one
Her sister said she was big
Shut up and wait here a sec
Uh, want coffee?
Don't worry, I promise no one's trying to poison you
Oh no
Forgive me, sir
I'm afraid I've missed the opportunity to destroy our enemy
Stop, hurting her isn't gonna solve anything
Thank you very much for your patience, commoners
Good news, Maria's just been offered a part-time specialty position
Huh?
That's nice, but what's a part-time specialty person do?
You teach classes part-time
So glad I have the greatest daddy in the world
No way
Serious?
I'm a real-life teacher, not just pretend?
Yep
Think you can handle it?
Totally!
Heck yeah!
Sweet
We'll add that to the paperwork, then
Yay, I'm a real teacher in a real school!
Oh, I'm a real teacher in the room
I'm a real teacher in the room
I'm a real wife over there
I'm a real markers and real racers
And I'll get out real grays and real stickers!
This is ridiculous!
I won't allow it!
Really?
Because the president of the school thinks it's fine
Because you didn't tell him the whole truth!
Just because you decided to get an advisor now
Doesn't mean the club wasn't founded illegally
It's still not legit!
Oh my god, shut your fly trap
Listen, and listen well
No matter how hard you work to get us shut down
I can still make a phone call and have it reversed
We have an advisor now, okay?
You're knocking paid off
You look like a hero
You're freaking welcome
I don't believe you!
You're lying about something!
You don't know when to quit, do you?
This club and everything in it is mine
I can do whatever I want
So if you keep pulling the student council crap
You won't be a member anymore
If you'd rather not deal, I can have you expelled
What?
But you can't expel me!
You want to test it and find out?
You better hope you're right
Sorry I ruined your meeting
I hope you can forgive me
And the club was saved by the rich girl
Who abused her power and threatened to have someone expelled
Well, I guess we know who the villain is
Whatever, at least I got it done and we still have a club
He made me Miss Kauru's bunny costume
Did you do that for the club
Or were you just trying to get back to your stupid bikini game?
Be honest, Senna
I was trying to finish the game
At least we know her priorities will always be the same
If that's all it took to get rid of her
Then she's totally not worth stopping the game to try to impress
If she was someone worthy of respect
She would have ignored me
And kept fighting for what she thought was actually right
I do sort of feel bad for little Aoi
But at least we know if Senna's around
The neighbor's club won't be shut down anytime soon
Oh, Kodaka, I have a question
Hmm?
Actually, Daddy reminded me of this when we were on the phone a little while ago
What?
Just curious
Would you ever reconsider marrying me?
It's been on my mind ever since the whole betrothal thing
I mean, I've told you before
I don't care about some stupid promise our fathers made to each other ages ago
That is still true, but this time it's different
Now, I don't care that the promise was made
Because even if it's what our parents want
It's what I want, too
And I wish I'd never called off the wedding
I know this seems kind of random
But I totes love you and stuff
It just kind of makes sense, you know?
I'm sorry it took me a while to realize it
What the hell are you saying?
Hey, you made me lose the entire game
I'm sorry?
So, what were you saying before?
Evs, I know you heard me
Whoa
I, uh, said that out loud, didn't I?
Well, I was planning to tell you sooner or later anyway
Wow, yeah
So, um, now you know
Let me know when you have an answer
Um, the, uh, that game you were playing
It's so loud I couldn't hear anything you said
What was it again?
Are you serious?
Sorry, there's an important errand I forgot to run
Ha!
Found you, demon Astaroth!
I have decided today I will use the magic
my teacher taught me to destroy you.
I admire your spirit, Guernica,
and respect your right to destroy me.
But you should know, I am your father.
What? You're a horse! How is that even possible?
It's actually a long story.
I don't want to know.
Hang on! One more and I'm out.
Join us next time for the final episode of Haganai Next,
I Blank Many Friends.
My enemy, Nine-Line Breaker!